A Guide to the Rockefeller foundation records, projects, SG 1.16-1.19 (A90-A93) FA469
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Foundation records, projects (A93), 1985-1993; 1.19; 121.03 Cubic Feet; 274 letter size document boxes and 1 legal size document box; Boxes 1-275
  - Special Interests and Explorations (SIE)
    - SIE 8728 - National Academy of Sciences - Committee on AIDS research, 1987-1989 (Box 249, Folder 1523)
    - SIE 8729 - Uwakaneme, Udochuku, 1987-1988, 1992 (Box 250, Folder 1524)
    - SIE 8730 - Aid to Artisans, Inc. - Market Link, 1984-1989. 1992 (Box 250, Folder 1525-1526)
    - SIE 8731 - Lihau, Ebua Marcel, 1987-1988, 1992 (Box 250, Folder 1527)
    - SIE 8733 - InterAction: American Council for Voluntary International Action, 1986-1989, 1992 (Box 250, Folder 1528-1529)
    - SIE 8735 - Stanford University - Indirect Cost Study, 1987, 1989-1991 (Box 250, Folder 1530)
    - SIE 8737 - National Commission on the Public Service, 1987-1990 (Box 250, Folder 1531, Box 251, Folder 1532-1534)
    - SIE 8740 - Mirabai Films, Inc. - "Good Morning Bombay", 1985-1989 (Box 251, Folder 1535-1536, Box 252, Folder 1537-1539)
    - SIE 8741 - WGBH Educational Foundation - State of the World Programs, 1985-1991 (Box 252, Folder 1540-1542)
    - SIE 8742 - American Academy of Arts and Sciences - International Development Conference, 1987-1989 (Box 252, Folder 1543)
    - SIE 8743 - City University of New York - Center for the Study of Philanthropy, 1987-1990 (Box 253, Folder 1544-1546)
    - SIE 8803 - South African Relief, 1987-1990 (Box 253, Folder 1547)
    - SIE 8813 - Interphil (International Standing Conference on Philanthropy), 1987-1990 (Box 253, Folder 1548)
    - SIE 8814 - South-North News Service, 1981-1990 (Box 254, Folder 1549-1553)
    - SIE 8817 - Institute for Research in History - Human Rights Conference, 1988, 1990 (Box 254, Folder 1554)
    - SIE 8818 - Rutgers University - "An Economic Evaluation of Corporate Philanthropic Support", 1988-1990 (Box 254, Folder 1555)
    - SIE 8820 - Aspen Institute (for Humanistic Studies) - Inter-American Dialogue, 1983-1992 (Box 255, Folder 1556-1561)
    - SIE 8821 - New York Academy of Sciences - Science Policy Association and Hi Tech/Business Forum, 1988-1990 (Box 256, Folder 1562)
    - SIE 8823 - Wider Opportunities for Women, Inc. - Resource Development Plan, 1988-1990. 1992 (Box 256, Folder 1563-1564)
    - SIE 8829 - Institute of International Education - South African Education Program, 1988-1990 (Box 256, Folder 1565-1566)
    - SIE 8831 - International Center for Research on Women - "Women and Economic Progress in the Third World: An Agenda", 1988-1990 (Box 256, Folder 1567)
    - SIE 8833 - Better World Society - "Babies Having Babies" Television Program, 1988, 1990, 1992 (Box 256, Folder 1568)
    - SIE 8834 - Sivard, Ruth Leger - World Priorities, 1975-1990, 1992 (Box 257, Folder 1569-1573, Box 258, Folder 1574-1577)
    - SIE 8834 - Sivard, Ruth Leger - World Priorities: Supplementary Material (Box 258, Folder 1578-1580, Box 259, Folder 1581-1585)
      Folders 1578-1580 - Spanish language distribution
    - SIE 8835 - World Resources Institute - "World Resources 1988-1989" Distribution, 1988-1990 (Box 259, Folder 1586)
    - SIE 8836 - African-American Institute, Inc. - South Africans Training, 1988-1991 (Box 260, Folder 1587)
    - SIE 8837 - Woods Hole Research Center - Climate Change Conferences, 1988-1990 (Box 260, Folder 1588)
    - SIE 8840 - Columbia University - Organized Philanthropy in East and Southeast Asia, 1988-1990 (Box 260, Folder 1589-1591)
    - SIE 8843 - Conflict Management Fund, Inc. - South African Negotiation Training, 1988-1990 (Box 260, Folder 1592)
    - SIE 8844 - Operation Crossroads Africa, Inc., 1988-1990 (Box 260, Folder 1593)
    - SIE 8845 - Center for Foreign Journalists - Third World Journalists Training, 1988-1990 (Box 261, Folder 1594-1595)
    - SIE 8847 - Children's Village - Child Information System, 1988-1990 (Box 261, Folder 1596)
    - SIE 8905 - Hunter College - Latinos in a Changing U.S. Economy, 1988-1990 (Box 261, Folder 1597)
    - SIE 8908 - Manhattan Institute for Policy Research - "Making Schools Better - The Challenge and Opportunity for New York City" Conference, 1989, 1991 (Box 261, Folder 1598)
    - SIE 8913 - Foundation for the Development of Polish Agriculture - International Task Force, 1989-1991 (Box 261, Folder 1599)
    - SIE 8914 - InterAction Council - European Forum on Forest Protection, 1988-1991 (Box 262, Folder 1600)
    - SIE 8916 - Indicator Media Training Project, 1989, 1991-1992 (Box 262, Folder 1601)
    - SIE 8918 - Rockefeller University - John D. Rockefeller 150th Anniversary Celebration, 1989, 1992 (Box 262, Folder 1602)
    - SIE 8922 - International Center of Photography - Midtown branch, 1989-1990, 1993 (Box 262, Folder 1603-1604)
    - SIE 8922 - International Center of Photography - Midtown Branch: Supplementary Material (Box 262, Folder 1605-1606)
    - SIE 8924 - Africa Fund - "Censored", a "South Africa Now" Television Special, 1989-1990 (Box 262, Folder 1607)
    - SIE 8925 - Operation Crossroads Africa, Inc. - Minority Student Internships, 1987-1989, 1991-1992 (Box 263, Folder 1608-1609)
    - SIE 8927 - Youth Project - Charles Bannerman Memorial Fellowship Program, 1989-1993 (Box 263, Folder 1610)
    - SIE 8928 - United Nations Association of the United States of America - UNESCO Study, 1987-1990, 1993 (Box 263, Folder 1611-1613)
      "Revitalizing International Scientific and Intellectual Cooperation - Re-examining the Mission of UNESCO"
    - SIE 8929 - Institute of Development Studies (Sussex) - Economic and Social Policies in Chile, 1989, 1991-1992 (Box 264, Folder 1614)
    - SIE 8930 - OEF International - African Regional Network for Women, 1989-1992 (Box 264, Folder 1615-1616)
      Formerly Overseas Education Fund
    - SIE 8933 - Tutu, Reverend Desmond M., 1988-1989, 1993 (Box 264, Folder 1617)
    - SIE 8935 - Harvard University - Gulf of Aqaba Environmental Conference, 1989-1990 (Box 264, Folder 1618)
    - SIE 8939 - Pesticide Education Center - Farm Worker Community Network, 1989-1994 (Box 264, Folder 1619-1620)
    - SIE 8940 - Michigan State University - School Leadership Academy, 1989, 1991-1992 (Box 264, Folder 1621)
    - SIE 8942 - University of New Mexico - Training Education Leaders, 1989-1990 (Box 265, Folder 1622)
    - SIE 8943 - Southwest Voter Registration Education Project - Willie Velasquez Family Fund, 1989, 1993 (Box 265, Folder 1623)
    - SIE 8946 - Council on Foundations, Inc. - Pluralism in Philanthropy, 1989-1991 (Box 265, Folder 1624)
    - SIE 8950 - New York Interface Development Project, Inc. - New York City Chancellor of Schools Transition, 1989-1990 (Box 265, Folder 1625)
    - SIE 8951 - Phillips Brooks House Association, Inc. - WorldTeach Program in Costa Rica, 1989-1991 (Box 265, Folder 1626)
    - SIE 8953 - International Maize and Wheat Improvement Center - Norman E. Borlaug's Memoirs, 1989-1991, 1993, 1996-1997 (Box 265, Folder 1627)
    - SIE 8954 - South African Committee for Higher Education Trust - Technical Education and Training, 1989-1990 (Box 265, Folder 1628)
    - SIE 8955 - Federal City Council - Comer Program in District of Columbia Schools, 1989, 1991 (Box 265, Folder 1629)
    - SIE 8957 - EVT Productions, Inc. - Comer Method Training Videos for School Administrators, 1989-1990, 1992 (Box 265, Folder 1630)
    - SIE 8959 - National AIDS Network - Fund, 1987-1990, 1992 (Box 265, Folder 1631, Box 266, Folder 1632-1634)
    - SIE 8960 - Philanthropic Initiative, Inc., 1989-1992 (Box 266, Folder 1635)
    - SIE 8967 - Parliamentarians for Global Action - Nuclear Test Ban, 1989-1990 (Box 266, Folder 1636)
    - SIE 8968 - Asian American Legal Defense and Education Fund - Civil Rights and Race Relations Course, 1989-1991, 1995 (Box 266, Folder 1637)
    - SIE 8969 - New York City Mayoral Transition Team, 1989-1990, 1993 (Box 267, Folder 1638)
    - SIE 8970 - International Human Rights Committee - Conference on South Africa, 1988-1992 (Box 267, Folder 1639)
    - SIE 8972 - Foundation for Social Innovations USA - San Francisco Office, 1989-1991 (Box 267, Folder 1640)
    - SIE 8973 - Stanford University - Community Service Requirement, 1989-1993 (Box 267, Folder 1641)
    - SIE 8706 - South African Committee for Higher Education Trust - Labour Education, 1982-1992 (Box 267, Folder 1642-1643, Box 268, Folder 1644)
      Formerly 155(489)
  - Special Programming (SP)
    - SP 8702 - United Nations Centre for Science and Technology for Development - China Seminar, 1987-1988, 1991-1992 (Box 268, Folder 1645)
    - SP 8704 - American Association for the Advancement of Science - Sub-Saharan Africa Infrastructure, 1987-1990 (Box 268, Folder 1646-1647)
    - SP 8705 - Harvard University - Independent International Commission on Health Research for Developing Countries, 1986-1987, 1989-1990 (Box 268, Folder 1648)
    - SP 8706 - Harvard University - Science, Engineering and Public Policy Workshop, 1987-1990 (Box 268, Folder 1649)
    - SP 8707- Australian National University - Health Transition in the Third World, 1987-1989, 1992, 1994 (Box 268, Folder 1650)
    - SP 8715 - University of Wisconsin - Contemporary Literature in Africa, 1987-1989 (Box 269, Folder 1651)
    - SP 8717 - International Consortium for Economic Research in Sub-Saharan Africa - Conference, 1987-1988 (Box 269, Folder 1652)
    - SP 8801 - Scripps Clinic and Research Foundation - Molecular Engineering, 1987-1989, 1991 (Box 269, Folder 1653)
    - SP 8802 - Panos Institute - Biotechnology and the Third World, 1987-1989 (Box 269, Folder 1654)
    - SP 8803 - Catholic University, Rio de Janeiro - Inter-American Seminar on Economics, 1987-1989 (Box 269, Folder 1655)
      Pontificia Universidade Catolica do Rio de Janeiro
    - SP 8805 - American Association for the Advancement of Science - Chinese Policy Makers Course, 1988-1989, 1991 (Box 269, Folder 1656)
    - SP 8807 - National University, Costa Rica - Economics Conference, 1987-1990 (Box 269, Folder 1657)
    - SP 8808 - Hoffman, Kurt, 1988-1989, 1991 (Box 269, Folder 1658)
      Literature review entitled "New Modes of Management and Production Organization: Exploring the Possibilities in Developing Countries"
    - SP 8811 - SNS-Center for Business and Policy Studies - Textile Trade Workshop, 1988-1991 (Box 269, Folder 1659)
    - SP 8812 - Centre for Applied Studies in International Negotiations - Uruguay Round Workshop, 1988-1991 (Box 269, Folder 1660)
    - SP 8815 - Scripps Clinic and Research Foundation - "Frontiers in Biomedical Research" Symposium, 1988-1989, 1991 (Box 270, Folder 1661)
    - SP 8822 - Council on Foreign Relations - Southern Africa Conference, 1988-1989 (Box 270, Folder 1662)
    - SP 8823 - World Bank - Development Economics Conference, 1988-1990 (Box 270, Folder 1663)
    - SP 8825 - Johns Hopkins University - Mahaweli Development Project Evaluation (Sri Lanka), 1988-1989, 1991 (Box 270, Folder 1664)
    - SP 8829 - Institute for International Economics - Debt Relief for Low Income Africa, 1988-1989, 1991, 1993-1994 (Box 270, Folder 1665)
    - SP 8834 - United Nations Research Institute for Social Development - Economic Crisis in the Third World Conference, 1988-1989, 1991-1992 (Box 270, Folder 1666)
    - SP 8901 - Freund, Gerald, 1988-1989, 1992, 1996 (Box 270, Folder 1667)
    - SP 8902 - Council on Ocean Law, 1984-1990, 1992 (Box 270, Folder 1668, Box 271, Folder 1669-1671)
    - SP 8904 - Sigma Xi, The Scientific Research Society - "Forum on Global Change and Our Common Future", 1989 (Box 271, Folder 1672)
    - SP 8906 - People's Government of Hainan Province - Environmental Preservation, 1988-1990 (Box 271, Folder 1673)
    - SP 8909 - American Committee on U.S.-Soviet Relations - Soviet Policy on the Environment, 1989-1990, 1992 (Box 271, Folder 1674-1675)
    - SP 8912 - Smithsonian Institution - Media Group and Environmental Conference, 1989-1991 (Box 271, Folder 1676)
    - SP 8913 - National Academy of Sciences - Board of Science and Technology for International Development (BOSTID) History Analysis, 1989-1991 (Box 272, Folder 1677)
    - SP 8915 - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Credit and Rural Development in India, 1989-1990 (Box 272, Folder 1678)
    - SP 8916 - American Farmland Trust - African Non-Governmental Organization Outreach Project, 1988-1990 (Box 272, Folder 1679-1681)
    - SP 8917 - Association for Women in Development - "Development Challenge of the 1990s: The Global Empowerment of Women" Conference, 1989, 1991 (Box 272, Folder 1682)
    - SP 8918 - World Bank - Kenya Education and Training, 1989, 1993, 1996 (Box 273, Folder 1683)
    - SP 8919 - Columbia University - African Data Bank, 1989-1990, 1992 (Box 273, Folder 1684)
    - SP 8921 - Opportunities Industrialization Centers International, Inc. - African Agricultural Programs, 1989-1991, 1993-1994 (Box 273, Folder 1685)
    - SP 8922 - People's Government of Hainan Province - Environmental and Natural Resources Conference, 1989-1990 (Box 273, Folder 1686-1687)
    - SP 8923 - Makerere University - "War Victim" Sculpture, 1988-1990, 1992-1993, 2000 (Box 273, Folder 1688)
      Artist Francis Xavier Nnagenda
    - SP 8924 - National Academy of Sciences - Mexican Environmental Problems, 1989-1991 (Box 273, Folder 1689)
    - SP 8925 - Freedom from Hunger Foundation - Chronic Hunger in Mali, 1989-1991, 1993 (Box 273, Folder 1690)
    - SP 8926 - University of Sao Paulo - Global Warming and Developing Countries Conference, 1988-1990, 1992 (Box 273, Folder 1691)
  - International Security (IS)
    - IS 8917 - Natural Resources Defense Council, Inc. - Nuclear Weapons at Sea, 1989-1990, 1992 (Box 274, Folder 1692)